Guide to the Fernando Alegria Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. Manuscripts by Alegria
  - Alegria, Fernando. Los grandes Reyes: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Guia de Chile: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Hernan Cortes (1485-1547): tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Hernandez Cata: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Himno de Manco Capac: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The Hispanic American aesthetic: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La historia de Enrique Huaco: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Historia de la filosofia: tms, n.d., 1 p. (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Horacio Quiroga: ams, n.d., 1 p. (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Hoy: tms (photocopy), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Huidobro: su obra poetica: tms, n.d., 18 p. (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El humor en la obra de Roque Dalton: tms, n.d., 19 p. (2 copies) (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Ideas esteticas de la poesía moderna. -- Santiago: Ediciones Multitud, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Ilario Da, relato en el frente chileno: [review]: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Informe]: tms, n.d., 16 p. (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Interview with Juan Rulfo]: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Introduccion. -- p. 37-39. -- In Hispamerica. -- Ano 1, no. 2 1972 Dec. (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Inventing history: introduction: tms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The inventive memory: autobiography: tms, n.d., 6 p. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Inventors of the country: tms (photocopy), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Jesucristo en Broadway: tms (photocopy), n.d., 3 p. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Jorge Caceres: ams. -- Braulio Arenas: ams, n.d., 1 p. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Jose Donoso: tms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Jose Revueltas' Los dias terrenales: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Juan Pablo en Chile: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Latin America: 1992: tms, n.d., 5 p. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Latin America: fantasy and reality: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Latin American authors]: fantasy and reality: ams & tms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Latin American literature: bibliography, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The Latin American revolution: tms and notes, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Lautaro: tms. -- Italian ed. [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Lautaro: tms. -- Italian ed. [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Lavin Cerda o la ferocidad del humor. -- p. 12-13. -- In Excelsior (Mexico) 1975 Aug. 24 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Let's hear it for Chile, God damn it!: trans. by Adele Negro, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Un libro de Betty La Duke: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Lineas torcidas: tms (photocopy), n.d., 20 p. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La literatura chilena contemporanea: tms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La literatura chilena en el contexto latinoamericano: tms, n.d., 10 p. (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Literatura y realidad actual en Latinoamerica: tms, n.d., 10 p. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Literatura y revolucion en Chile: tms, n.d., 24 p. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Literatura y revolucion en Chile: tms & correspondence, 1976, 3 tms + 3 tls (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Contains drafts of three chapters of Alegria's book, Literatura y revolucion, translated by J. Douglas Ohmans and the accompanying correspondence from Ohmans.
  - Alegria, Fernando. The little architects of the Sand City: original tms, n.d., 14 p. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The little architects of the Sand City: tms, n.d., 14 p. (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Luces en la isla: J.A. Epple y sus poetas: tms, n.d., 6 p. (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Luis Merino Reyes, Murcila, y otros cuentos. -- p. 171-172. -- In Revista Iberoamericana. -- Vol. 19, no. 37 1953 Oct. (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Luis Merino Reyes, Regazo Amargo: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Luis Merino Reyes' Ultima llama, 1959: tms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Magic realism: abstract of essay: tms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Magic realism and the Latin American reality: tms, n.d., 14 p. (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Magic realism and the Latin American reality: tms, n.d., 14 p. (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Magic realism and the Latin American reality: tms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Mañana los guerreros: en ingles: tms [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Mañana los guerreros: en ingles: tms [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Mañana los guerreros: en ingles: tms [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Mancha de aceite [por] Cesar Uribe-Piedralita: ams, ca. 1935 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El Manguito: tms, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Manuel Magallanes Moure (1878-1924): tms, n.d., 17 p. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La maratón del palomo. -- p. 5-35 n.d. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La maratón del palomo: clipping n.d. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Matilde Ladrón de Guevara, La ciénaga: tms, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The maypole warrior: tms [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The maypole warrior: tms [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Memoria: partial tms: p. 20-23 n.d. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Memoria creadora y autobiografía en Latinoamérica: Darío y Neruda: tms, n.d., 25 p. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La memoria creadora: novela y poesía autobiográficas en Latinoamerica: tms, n.d., 22 p. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Memorias de la libertad: una novela que canta: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Mempo Giaridinelli]: tms with holograph annotations, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Mesoamerica: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Mi estudio: tms (photocopy), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Mi libro favorito: tms, n.d. -- Entrevista: tms, n.d., 2 p. (2 copies); 8 p. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Miguel A. Asturias: tms, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Miguel Arteche (1926): tms, n.d., 9 p. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Miscellaneous poems n.d. (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El modernismo en Chile: tms, n.d., 13 p. (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The most significant decade in Latin American fiction: clipping (photocopy) n.d. (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Muerte y resurreción: tms, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Una mujer en llamas: tms, n.d., 9 p. (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Una mujer en llamas: tms, n.d., 102 p. (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Muñeca brava: Lucía Guerra: tms, n.d., 6 p. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Muñeca brava: Lucía Guerra: tms, n.d., 6 p. (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Museo Hualpán: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. My horse Gonzalez: correspondence, request for review, clippings n.d. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La narrativa chilena del exilio interior: tms, n.d., 20 p. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Naufragio [por] Juan Marin: ams, n.d., 2 p. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Neruda: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Neruda in Mexico: 1940-1943: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Neruda y La Araucana: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Neruda's circles: tms, n.d., 11 p. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Neruda's circles: tms, n.d., 11 p. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Neruda's circles: tms, n.d., 9 p.; 4 p. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. New Latin American fiction: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El nobel del gabo: tms (photocopy), n.d., 3 p. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Las noches del cazador: novela: first draft tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Novela: fragment tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Novela: fragment tms, p. 27-34 ca. 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La novela chilena del exilio interior: tms, n.d., 15 p. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La novela chilena del exilio interior: tms, n.d., 13 p. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La novela hispanoamericana: 1960-1988: tms, n.d., 35 p. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La novela hispanoamericana: Siglo XX: notes, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La novela hispanoamericana: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Nuestro destino manifesto: tms [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Nuestro destino manifesto: tms [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Nuevas poemas ineditas: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Un nuevo amor: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Un nuevo libro: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Octavio Paz: Sor Juana: tms, n.d., 4 p. (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Octubres del Otoño: biografias clandestinas. -- In Excelsior 198- Mar. 31 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Omar Cabezas]: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. On what side of the screen?: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La otra imagen de Latinoamerica: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Los p[?] perdidos: ams, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Pablo de Rokha (1894-1968): tms, n.d., 12 p. (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Pablo Neruda escribe sus memorias: tms, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Paisano Aguilar [por] Enrique Amorian: ams, ca. 1934 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Pampa brava [por] Andres Garaf[lio?]: ams, ca. 1935 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Paola Andrade: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Pedro Antonio Gonzalez (1863-1903): tms, n.d., 24 p. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Pedro de Valdivia, personaje literario: tms, n.d., 37 p. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Pedro Fuentes: cuentos de villanos: tms, n.d., 3 p. (2 copies) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Pedro Paramo por Juan Rulfo: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La Pitonisa: tms, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Pluma y lapiz: bibliografia n.d. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El poema: narrativa breve: tms, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Poemas, nuevo: tms, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - [Alegria, Fernando]. [Poems]: tms, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena del Siglo XX: outlines, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena del Siglo XX: treatment, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena del Siglo XX: notebook, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena del Siglo XX: partial draft tms: pp. 156-224, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena del Siglo XX: research & notes n.d. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: tms [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: tms [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: tms [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: notes, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: indice, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: indice, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: partial draft, 1997 Sept. 6 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: partial tms: pp. 1-76 n.d., 1 v., spiral bound (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: partial tms: pp. 1-77; 194-224 n.d., 1 v., spiral bound (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: partial tms: pp. 160-193 n.d., 1 v., spiral bound (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: partial tms: pp. 292-505 + misc. n.d., 1 v., spiral bound (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: bibliografía n.d. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: bibliografía minima, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: bibliography 1977 May (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Amor y desamor: la poesia de Enrique Lihn (1929-1988): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Eduardo Anguita (1914): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Eduardo Anguita (1914-1992): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Miguel Arteche (1926): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Julio Barrenechea (1910-1970): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: La Barcarola: barca de la vida: tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Efrain Barquero (1931): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: El barroco chileno: primera mitad del Siglo XX: tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: El barroco chileno: tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Javier Campos (1947): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Collecion de poesia chilena: catalogo 1: tms [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Collecion de poesia chilena: catalogo 1: tms [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Angel Cruchaga Santa Maria (1893-1954): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Angel Cruchaga Santa Maria (1893-1954): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Díaz Casanueva: tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Humberto Díaz Casanueva (1907-1992): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Delia Dominguez (1931): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Diego Duble Urrutia (1877-1967): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Diego Duble Urrutia (1877-1967): tms, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Aristoteles España (1956): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Fin de Siglo: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Garcia Lorca pasa por Rancagua: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Domingo Gómez Rojas (1896-1920): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Antonio González (1863-1903): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Antonio González (1863-1903): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Antonio González: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Antonio González (1863-1903): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Oscar Hahn (1938): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Vicente Huidobro: la vanguardia (1903): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Huidobro: su obra poética (1893-1948): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Vicente Huidobro (1893-1948): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Vicente Huidobro: la vanguardia: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Omar Lara (1941): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Lastra (1932): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Enrique Lihn (1929): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Enrique Lihn: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Manuel Magallanes Moore (1878-1924): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Manuel Magallanes Moore (1878-1924): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Manuel Magallanes Moore (1878-1924): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Manuel Magallanes Moore (1878-1924): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Diego Maquieira (1951): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Jose Maria Memet (1957): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Jose Maria Memet (1957): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Mahfud Massis (1917-1992): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Gonzalo Millán (1947): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Gabriela Mistral (1889-1957): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Gabriela Mistral (1889-1957): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Gabriela Mistral (1889-1957): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Hugo Montes: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Maria Monvel (1899-1936): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Maria Monvel (1899-1936): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Parabolas, simbolos, mensajes: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Nicanor Parra (1914): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Nicanor Parra (1914): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Carlos Pezoa Véliz (1879-1908): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Carlos Pezoa Véliz (1879-1908): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Carlos Pezoa Véliz (1879-1908): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Carlos Pezoa Véliz: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Carlos Pezoa Véliz: tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Maria Elvira Powonka (1909): tms, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Prado (1866-1952): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Prado (1866-1952): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Prado (1866-1952): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pedro Prado (1866-1952): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Prefacio: tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Proyecto Rockalita: tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Chela Reyes: tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Domingo Gomez Rojas (1896-1920): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Gonzalo Rojas (1917): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Gonzalo Rojas (1917): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Manuel Rojas (1896-1973): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Manuel Rojas (1896-1973): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Manuel Rojas (1896-1973): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Alberto Rojas Jimenez (1900-1933): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Alberto Rojas Jimenez (1900-1933): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Salvador Salazar Arrué (1899-1975): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pablo de Rokha (1894-1968): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Pablo de Rokha (1894-1968): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Winnett de Rokha (1894-1951): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Winnett de Rokha (1894-1951): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Runrunismo: tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: La ruta de Pedro Prado y Juan Guzman Cruchaga: tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: La semilla en la sombra: el arte de Pablo Neruda (1904-1973): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Surrealismo en la generación del 38: tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Jorge Teillier (1935): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Guillermo Trejo (1926): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Armando Urribe (1933): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Juvencio Valle (1900): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Juvencio Valle (1900): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Rosamel del Valle (1900-1965): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La poesia chilena en el Siglo XX: Rosamel del Valle (1900-1965): tms, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 31)